Guide to the Linda Mary Montano Papers, 1931-2014 MSS.386
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series X: Library, 1931-2013; 6 Linear Feet in 5 record cartons and 2 manuscript boxes.
  - Doyle, Jennifer. Hold it against me: difficulty and emotion in contemporary art. Durham; London: Duke University Press, 2013 (Box 96, Folder 15)
  - Drobnick, Jim; Fisher, Jennifer. Museopathy. Agnes Etherington Art Centre, 2001 (Box 96, Folder 16)
  - Estevez, Nicolas Dumit, (Ed.). Life as material for art and vice versa. New York: Queens Museum of Art, 2011 (Box 96, Folder 17)
  - Evans, Bessie and Evans, May G. American Indian Dance Steps. New York, A. S. Barnes & Co, Inc., 1931 (Box 96, Folder 18)
  - Fitzgerald, f/Stop. Documentia. San Francisco: Last Gasp of San Francisco, 1987 (Box 96, Folder 19)
  - Fernett, Gene. A Thousand Golden Horns. Midland, MI: Pendell Company, 1966 (Box 96, Folder 20)
  - Fisher, Jennifer. Technologies of intuition. Toronto: YYZ Books, 2006 (Box 96, Folder 21)
  - Gamper, Gisela and Pollack, Rachel. Fabrications. Barrytown, NY: Barrytown Ltd., 1997 (Box 96, Folder 22)
  - Glass, Liz, Magers, Susannah, and Myers, Julian. Give Them The Picture: An Anthology of La Mamelle and ART COM 1975-1984. CCA Wattis Institute for Contemporary Arts, undated (Box 96, Folder 23)
  - Graves, Ken and Payne, Mitchell. American Snapshots. Oakland, CA: Scrimshaw Press, 1977 (Box 96, Folder 24)
  - Hammond, Harmony. Wrappings: Essays on Feminism, Art, and the Martial Arts. New York: TSL Press, 1984 (Box 96, Folder 25)
  - Haines, Frank. Frank exchanges. [place of publication unknown: publisher unknown], 2014 (Box 96, Folder 26)
  - Hay, Deborah. My body, the Buddhist. Hanover, N.H.: University Press of New England; Wesleyan University Press, 2000 (Box 97, Folder 1)
  - Hay, Deborah. Lamb at the altar: The story of a dance. Durham, NC: Duke University Press, 1994 (Box 97, Folder 2)
  - Highwater, Jamake. Ritual of the wind: North American Indian Ceremonies, Music, and Dances. New York: The Viking Press, 1977 (Box 97, Folder 3)
  - Huffman, Kathy Rae. Video: a retrospective: Long Beach Museum of Art, 1974-1984. Long Beach, CA: Long Beach Museum of Art (Box 97, Folder 4)
  - Kastner, Jeffrey. Nature. London: Whitechapel Gallery; Cambridge, MA: MIT Press, 2012 (Box 97, Folder 5)
  - Keyes, Ken, Jr. Taming Your Mind. Berkeley: Living Love Center, 1975 (Box 97, Folder 6)
  - LeBar, James J., Rev. Cults, sects, and the new age. Huntingdon, IN: Our Sunday Visitor Publishing Division, 1989 (Box 97, Folder 7)
  - LeSueur, Meridel. Rites of Ancient Ripening. Minneapolis: Vanilla Press Inc., 1975 (Box 97, Folder 8)
  - Lewallen, Constance. Space, time, sound: conceptual art in the San Francisco Bay Area, the 1970s. San Francisco: San Francisco Museum of Modern Art, 1981 (Box 97, Folder 9)
  - Lewallen, Constance M. and Moss, Karen. State of Mind: New California Art circa 1970. Berkeley: University of California Press, 2011 (Box 97, Folder 10)
  - Loeffler, Carl E and Tong, Darlene. Performance anthology: source book for a decade of California performance art. San Francisco, CA: Contemporary Arts Press, 1980 (Box 97, Folder 11)
  - Marioni, Tom. Sculptures and Installations: 1969-1997, undated (Box 97, Folder 12)
  - Mark, Lisa Gabrielle and Schimmel, Paul. Under the Big Black Sun: California Art 1974-1981. Los Angeles: Museum of Contemporary Art; Munich: DelMonico Books, Prestel, 2011 (Box 97, Folder 13)
  - Marranca, Bonnie. Performance Histories. New York: PAJ Publications, 2007 (Box 97, Folder 14)
  - Mendieta, Ana. Ana Mendieta: She Got Love. Milano, Italy: Skira, 2013 (Box 97, Folder 15)
  - Merali, Shaheen (Ed.). New York: states of mind: art in the city. London: Saqi, 2008 (Box 97, Folder 16)
  - Miller, Lynn C., Taylor, Jacqueline, and Carver, Heather (Eds.). Voices made flesh: performing women's autobiography. Madison, WI: University of Wisconsin Press, 2003 (Box 97, Folder 17)
  - Montano, Linda. The Art/Life Institute Handbook. Saugerties, NY: Arts/Life Institute, 1988 (Box 97, Folder 18)
  - Montano, Linda. You too are a performance artists. Santa Fe, NM: SITE Santa Fe, 2013 (Box 98, Folder 1)
  - Myers, Roger. Guide to archival materials of the center for creative photography. Tuscon, Arizona, University of Arizona, 1986 (Box 98, Folder 2)
  - Nemec, Vernita. Private Thoughts/Private Places, 1984 (Box 98, Folder 3)
  - Norman, Howard A. The Wishing Bone Cycle. New York, Stonehill Publishing Company, 1976 (Box 98, Folder 4)
  - Oliveros, Pauline. The roots of the moment. New York: Drogue Press, 1998 (Box 98, Folder 5)
  - Oliveros, Pauline. Software for people: collected writings 1963-80. Baltimore, MD: Smith Publications; Barrytown, NY: Printed Editions, 1984 (Box 98, Folder 6)
  - Oliveros, Pauline and Cohen, Becky. Initiation Dream. Los Angeles, Astro Artz, 1981 (Box 98, Folder 7)
  - Phillips, Lisa. The American Century: Art & Culture, 1950-2000. New York: Whitney Museum of American Art in association with Norton, 1999 (Box 98, Folder 8)
  - Re/Search Publications. Angry Women. Re/Search Publications, 1991 (Box 98, Folder 9)
  - Reigns, Steven. Your dead body is my welcome mat. Burning Page Press, 2001 (Box 98, Folder 10)
  - Reigns, Steven (Ed.). My life is poetry: an anthology of writings by gay, lesbian, and bisexual seniors. Los Angeles: Grenadier Press, 2008 (Box 98, Folder 11)
  - Richman, Gary. Offset: a survey of artists' books. Cambridge, MA: New England Foundation for the Arts, 1984 (Box 98, Folder 12)
  - Rosen, Randy and Brawer, Catherine C. Making their mark: women artists move into the mainstream, 1970-85. New York: Abbeville Press, 1989 (Box 98, Folder 13)
  - Roth, Moira. The amazing decade: women and performance art in America, 1970-1980. Los Angeles: Astro Artz, 1983 (Box 98, Folder 14)
  - Roth, Moira (Ed.). Connecting Conversations: Interviews with 28 Bay Area Women Artists. Oakland, CA: Eucalyptus Press Mills College, 1988 (Box 98, Folder 15)
  - Rothenberg, Jerome. Technicians of the sacred: A range of poetries from Africa, America, Asia, Europe & Oceania. Berkeley: University of California Press, 1985 (Box 98, Folder 16)
  - Rothenberg, Jerome. Poetics & Polemics: 1980-2005. Tuscaloosa, AL: University of Alabama Press, 2008 (Box 98, Folder 17)
  - Rugoff, Ralph. Extra art: a survey of artists' ephemera, 1960-1999. Santa Monica: Smart Art Press, 2001 (Box 98, Folder 18)
  - Sands. Profeminist WHITE FLOWERS, 2007 (Box 98, Folder 19)
  - Schneemann, Carolee. Imaging her erotics: essays, interviews, projects. Cambridge, MA: MIT Press, 2002 (Box 98, Folder 20)
  - Schroeder, Johannes Lothar. Blende und traumzeit. Kiel: NONOMPRESS, 1992 (Box 98, Folder 21)
  - Shigemi, Inaga. Questioning Oriental Aesthetics and Thinking: Conflicting Vision of "Asia" under the Colonial Empire. Kyoto, International Research Center for Japanese Studies, 2011 (Box 99, Folder 1)
  - Smith, Terry. Contemporary Art: World Currents. Upper Saddle River, NJ: Prentice Hall, 2011 (Box 99, Folder 2)
  - Solomon-Godeau, Abigail, Montano, Linda, Princenthal, Nancy, and Sabbatino, Mary. Ana Mendieta: Blood & Fire. Paris/New York: Galerie LeLong, undated (Box 99, Folder 3)
  - Tisdall, Caroline, and Beuys, Joseph. Joseph Beuys. Thames and Hudson, London, for the Guggenheim Museum, New York, 1979 (Box 99, Folder 4)
  - Vera, Veronica. Miss Vera's finishing school for boys who want to be girls. New York: Doubleday, 1997 (Box 99, Folder 5)
  - Villines, Melanie. Windy City Sinners: a novel. Chicago, IL: Inklings Press, 2011 (Box 99, Folder 6)
  - Villines, Melanie. Tales of the Sacred Heart: a novel. Libertyville, IL: Bogfire, 1999 (Box 99, Folder 7)
  - Vincent, Stephen and Zweig, Ellen. The Poetry reading: a contemporary compendium on language & performance. San Francisco: Momo's Press, 1981 (Box 99, Folder 8)
  - Von Gunden, Heidi. The music of Pauline Oliveros. Metuchen, NJ: Scarecrow Press, 1983 (Box 99, Folder 9)
  - Wark, Jayne. Radical gestures feminism and performance art in North America. Montreal: McGill-Queen's University Press, 2006 (Box 99, Folder 10)
  - Warr, Tracey and Jones, Amelia. The artist's body. London: Phaidon, 2000 (Box 99, Folder 10)
  - Weintraub, Linda and Schuckmann, Skip. ECOcentric Topics: pioneering themes for eco-art. Rhinebeck, NY: ArtNow Publications, 2006 (Box 99, Folder 11)
  - Wexler, Alice. Art education beyond the classroom: pondering the outsider and other sites of learning. New York; Houndmills, Basingstoke, Hampshire England: Palgrave Macmillan, 2012 (Box 99, Folder 12)
  - Wise, Nina. A big new free happy unusual life. New York: Broadway Books, 2001 (Box 99, Folder 13)
  - Zwehl-Burke, Pamela and Fedorchuk, Leslie. Women's Autobiographical Artists' Books. University of Wisconsin, Milwaukee Art Museum Fine Arts Galleries and the Conference Center of the Golda Meir Library, 1987 November (Box 99, Folder 14)
  - Con el cuerpo por delante: 47882 minutos de performance. Mexico: Instituto Nacional de Bellas Artes, 2001 (Box 99, Folder 15)
  - Voices from the edge: conversations with Jerry Garcia, Ram Dass, Annie Sprinkle, Matthew Fox, Jaron Lanier & Others. California: The Crossing Press Freedom, 1995 (Box 99, Folder 16)
  - Find-A-Text Puzzle Fun: Art World Edition. New York: Art-Text Enterprises, 2008 (Box 99, Folder 17)
  - Aeroports Magazine. No. 8, 2006 March (Box 100, Folder 1)
  - Americana. Vol. 6 No. 1, 1978 March-April (Box 100, Folder 2)
  - Art in America, 1984 September (Box 100, Folder 3)
  - Art in America, 2007 June-July (Box 100, Folder 3)
  - Art in America, 2009 April (Box 100, Folder 4)
  - Art in America, 2013 June-July (Box 100, Folder 4)
  - Artforum. Vol. 22 No. 2, 1983 October (Box 100, Folder 5)
  - Artforum. Summer, 1983 (Box 100, Folder 5)
  - ArtLies, 2002 (Box 100, Folder 6)
  - Ascent. Issue 24, Winter, 2004 (Box 100, Folder 7)
  - Cabinet: A Quarterly of Art and Culture. Issue 14, 2004 (Box 100, Folder 8)
  - Camerawork. Vol. 30 No.1 Spring/Summer, 2003 (Box 100, Folder 9)
  - Crawl Out Your Window. Vol. 7, 1980 July (Box 100, Folder 10)
  - Crawl Out Your Window. Vol. 9/10, 1982 May (Box 100, Folder 10)
  - Dialogue: An Art Journal. Vol. 12 No. 4, 1989 July-August (Box 100, Folder 11)
  - Dystonia. Vol. 12 No. 1, 2009 January (Box 100, Folder 12)
  - Five Fingers Review. Issue 10, 1991 (Box 100, Folder 13)
  - Front. Vol. 14 No. 4, 2003 September-October (Box 100, Folder 14)
  - Harpers. Vol. 279 No. 1670, 1989 July (Box 100, Folder 15)
  - LA Weekly. Vol. 35 No. 35, 2013 July (Box 100, Folder 16)
  - Live. Issue 3, 1980 (Box 100, Folder 17)
  - Branca, Glenn. Live 6/7, 1982 (Box 100, Folder 18)
  - New Observations. No. 112, Fall, 1996 (Box 100, Folder 18)
  - New Observations. No. 108, 1995 September-October (Box 100, Folder 18)
  - New Performance. Vol. 1 No. 3, 1978 (Box 100, Folder 19)
  - New Wilderness Letter. Vol. 2 No. 7, Summer, 1979 (Box 100, Folder 20)
  - PAJ: A Journal of Performance and Art. Vol. 34 No. 1, 2012 January (Box 100, Folder 21)
  - PAJ: A Journal of Performance and Art. Vol. 23, No. 3, 2001 September (Box 100, Folder 21)
  - Parachute. Issue 64, 1991 October (Box 100, Folder 22)
  - Parachute. Issue 80, 1995 October-December (Box 100, Folder 22)
  - Pasatiempo, 2013 February (Box 100, Folder 23)
  - Performing Arts Journal. Vol. 4, No. 3 (Issue 12), undated (Box 100, Folder 24)
  - Pform. No. 38, 1995-1996 (Box 100, Folder 25)
  - Pform. No. 45, 1998 (Box 100, Folder 25)
  - Profile. Vol. 4 No. 6, 1984 December (Box 100, Folder 26)
  - College of New Rochelle. Quarterly. Spring/Summer, 1984 (Box 100, Folder 27)
  - Satori. Vol. 1 No. 3, Winter, 1989 (Box 100, Folder 28)
  - Signature. Vol. 5 No. 2, Winter, 1967 (Box 100, Folder 29)
  - Spy: The New York Monthly, 1987 November (Box 100, Folder 30)
  - Sulfur. Issue 22, Spring, 1988 (Box 100, Folder 31)
  - The Act. Vol. 1 No. 3, 1988-1989 (Box 100, Folder 32)
  - Center for Creative Photography. The Archive. No. 17, 1983 March (Box 100, Folder 33)
  - The Cherotic (r)evolutionary. Vol. 1 Issue 8, undated (Box 100, Folder 34)
  - The Drama Review: TDR. Vol. 23 No. 1, 1979 March (Box 100, Folder 35)
  - The Drama Review: TDR. Vol. 30 No. 1, Spring, 1986 (Box 100, Folder 35)
  - The Drama Review: TDR. Vol. 33 No. 1, Spring, 1989 (Box 100, Folder 36)
  - The Drama Review: TDR. Vol. 56 No. 4, 2012 (Box 100, Folder 36)
  - The Dumb Ox. Issue 10/11, Spring, 1980 (Box 100, Folder 37)
  - The Sunday Times Magazine, 1984 July 1 (Box 100, Folder 38)
  - Ulster. Spring, 1994 (Box 100, Folder 39)
  - Working Paper. Issue 2, 1981 November (Box 100, Folder 40)
  - Creative Arts '67. University of Wisconsin, Spring, 1967 (Box 101, Folder 1)
  - Video Data Bank. Video Tape Review. Issue 86, undated (Box 101, Folder 2)
  - 1ere Semaine Internationale de Video Geneve - Suisse, 1985 (Box 101, Folder 3)
  - American Film Institute. National Video Festival: Olympic Screenings, 1984 September (Box 101, Folder 4)
  - Artists Space. Unacceptable Appetites, 1988 (Box 101, Folder 5)
  - Arts Society of Kingston. Kingston Sculpture Biennial, 2007 (Box 101, Folder 6)
  - Cohn, Terri. Artist's Response: Portraits and Self-Portraits, 2010 (Box 101, Folder 7)
  - Everson Museum of Art. Figures: Form and fiction, 1988 (Box 101, Folder 8)
  - Institute of Contemporary Arts. Rapture: The body, ritual + sacred practice. London, undated (Box 101, Folder 9)
  - Montano, Linda. Pinata Project, undated (Box 101, Folder 10)
  - Museo de Arte Contemporaneo. Como virir juntos: Selection 27a Bienal de Sao Paulo, 2007 (Box 101, Folder 11)
  - San Francisco Art Institute. The Annual: September 12, 1975 - August 27, 1976, 1977 (Box 101, Folder 12)
  - Singh, Victoria (Ed.). Ritual in contemporary performance: Western front performance art contemporary ritual series, 2004 (Box 101, Folder 13)
  - Everson Video Revue, 1979 (Box 101, Folder 14)
  - Personal Histories, 1988 March (Box 101, Folder 15)
  - Sprinkle, Annie. Love and kisses from Annie Sprinkle: volume 2. New York, Gates of Heck, 1997 (Box 101, Folder 16)
  - Sprinkle, Annie. Love and kisses from Annie Sprinkle: volume 1. New York: Gates of Heck, 1997 (Box 101, Folder 16)
  - Santa Cruz film festival program, 2008 May (Box 102, Folder 1)
  - Zen Mountain Center of New York. Mountain Record. Summer, 1985 (Box 102, Folder 2)
  - Zen Mountain Center of New York. Mountain Record. Fall, 1984 (Box 102, Folder 2)
  - Ananda Ashram: Yoga Society of New York. Summer Program Guide, 2005 (Box 102, Folder 3)
  - Center for Creative Photography. Annual Report, 2011-2012 (Box 102, Folder 4)
  - The Minnette Files. San Francisco: The Lab, 2000 (Box 102, Folder 5)
  - Almanac Weekly, October 2013 (Box 113, Folder 4)
  - Almanac Weekly, October 2012 (Box 113, Folder 3)
  - ALOP, 2011 (Box 116, Folder 5)
  - And/Or Notes, March 1980 (Box 108, Folder 1)
  - Art Times, Spring 2013 (Box 116, Folder 4)
  - Artist's Body, The, 2000 (Box 116, Folder 12)
  - B., Franko. Franko B: Blinded by Love, 2007 (Box 115, Folder 10)
  - Beverly Ogdon on Swinging, 1981 (Box 108, Folder 2)
  - Binnewater Tides, The, Fall 1992 (Box 114, Folder 2)
  - Binnewater Tides, The, Summer 1991 (Box 114, Folder 1)
  - Brooklyn Rail, The, February 2012 (Box 113, Folder 7)
  - Bry, Doris. Alfred Stieglitz: Photographer, 1965 (Box 113, Folder 6)
  - Chronogram, May 2014 (Box 112, Folder 11)
  - Chronogram, December 2008 (Box 112, Folder 5)
  - Brooklyn Rail, The, July-August 2013 (Box 113, Folder 6)
  - Chronogram, January 2013 (Box 112, Folder 9)
  - Chronogram, September 2013 (Box 112, Folder 10)
  - Chronogram, October 2000 (Box 112, Folder 1)
  - Chronogram, October 2010 (Box 112, Folder 8)
  - Chronogram, July 2007 (Box 112, Folder 4)
  - Chronogram, September 2013 (Box 112, Folder 6)
  - Chronogram, October 2009 (Box 112, Folder 7)
  - Chronogram, March 2007 (Box 112, Folder 2)
  - Chronogram, June 2006 (Box 112, Folder 3)
  - Ear Magazine, November 1982-January 1983 (Box 115, Folder 7)
  - Ear Magazine, June-August 1981 (Box 115, Folder 6)
  - East Bay Express, May 2012 (Box 114, Folder 3)
  - Explore Hudson Valley, October 2012 (Box 115, Folder 3)
  - Flue (Box 115, Folder 4)
  - Franklin Furnace. Sex, Performance, and the 80s, 1982 (Box 108, Folder 3)
  - Goldberg, Roselee. Performance, 1998 (Box 115, Folder 8)
  - Hallwalls, December 1996 (Box 115, Folder 5)
  - Heart Before Art/Life Counseling, A, 1983 (Box 108, Folder 4)
  - High Performance V.7 No. 3 (Box 108, Folder 19)
  - High Performance V.7 No. 4 (Box 108, Folder 20)
  - HIgh Performance V.5 No. 1 (Box 108, Folder 12)
  - HIgh Performance V.8 No. 1 (Box 109, Folder 1)
  - HIgh Performance V.9 No. 2 (Box 109, Folder 4)
  - HIgh Performance V.5 No. 4 (Box 108, Folder 13)
  - HIgh Performance V.6 No. 1 (Box 108, Folder 14)
  - HIgh Performance V.6 No. 2 (Box 108, Folder 15)
  - HIgh Performance V.12 No. 2 (Box 109, Folder 14)
  - HIgh Performance V.12 No. 3 (Box 109, Folder 15)
  - HIgh Performance V.8 No. 4 (Box 109, Folder 2)
  - HIgh Performance V.9 No. 1 (Box 109, Folder 3)
  - HIgh Performance V.6 No. 4 (Box 108, Folder 16)
  - HIgh Performance V.7 No. 1 (Box 108, Folder 17)
  - HIgh Performance V.7 No. 2 (Box 108, Folder 18)
  - HIgh Performance V.1 No. 4 (Box 108, Folder 5)
  - HIgh Performance V.3 No. 3 and 4 (Box 108, Folder 7)
  - HIgh Performance V.4 No. 1 (Box 108, Folder 8)
  - HIgh Performance V.4 No. 2 (Box 108, Folder 9)
  - HIgh Performance V.13 No. 1 (Box 109, Folder 16)
  - HIgh Performance V.4 No. 4 (Box 108, Folder 11)
  - HIgh Performance V.11 No. 3 (Box 109, Folder 12)
  - HIgh Performance V.11 No. 4 (Box 109, Folder 13)
  - HIgh Performance V.2 No. 3 (Box 108, Folder 6)
  - HIgh Performance V.9 No. 3 (Box 109, Folder 5)
  - HIgh Performance V.9 No. 4 (Box 109, Folder 6)
  - HIgh Performance V.10 No. 1 (Box 109, Folder 7)
  - HIgh Performance V.10 No. 2 (Box 109, Folder 8)
  - HIgh Performance V.10 No. 3 (Box 109, Folder 9)
  - HIgh Performance V.10 No. 4 (Box 109, Folder 10)
  - HIgh Performance V.11 No. 1 and 2 (Box 109, Folder 11)
  - Italian Cooking, 2011 (Box 109, Folder 17)
  - La momelle, Spring 1976 (Box 114, Folder 4)
  - Magazine, The, February/March 2013 (Box 116, Folder 1)
  - Magazine, The, April 2013 (Box 116, Folder 3)
  - Magazine, The, May 2013 (Box 116, Folder 2)
  - Montano, Lina M. The Art/life institute handbook (Box 110, Folder 4)
  - Montano, Linda M. Letters from Linda M. Montano, 2005 (Box 110, Folder 5)
  - Montano, Linda M. Performance artists of the eighties, 2000 (Box 110, Folder 6)
  - Montano, Linda M. Profile, December 1984 (Box 110, Folder 8)
  - Montano, Linda M. The Wisdom of Mataji & Bapuji, February 2000 (Box 110, Folder 10)
  - Montano, Linda M. The Wisdom of Mataji & Bapuji, February 2000 (Box 110, Folder 11)
  - Montano, Linda. Art in Everyday Life, 1981 (Box 110, Folder 3)
  - Montano, Linda. Performance artists talking in the eighties, 2000 (Box 110, Folder 7)
  - Montano, Linda. The 5 Johns of John Street (Box 110, Folder 1)
  - Montano, Linda. The 5 Johns of John Street (Box 110, Folder 2)
  - Montano, Linda. Twelve Poems (Box 110, Folder 9)
  - Munroe, Alexander. The Third Mind, 2009 (Box 114, Folder 6)
  - N. Paradoxa, 2000 (Box 110, Folder 12)
  - N. Paradoxa, 2015 (Box 110, Folder 13)
  - Pauline's Proverbs, Christmas 1976 (Box 110, Folder 14)
  - Power of Feminist Art, The, 1994 (Box 110, Folder 15)
  - Santa Fe Reporter, February 2013 (Box 115, Folder 1)
  - Santa Fe Reporter, May 2013 (Box 115, Folder 2)
  - Schimmel, Paul. Out of actions, 1998 (Box 111, Folder 1)
  - Signature, Spring 1967 (Box 111, Folder 2)
  - Site-Specific Artworks, 1994 (Box 116, Folder 11)
  - Sprinkle, Annie. Hardcore from the Heart, 2001 (Box 111, Folder 3)
  - Sprinkle, Annie. Love Vibration, 1996 (Box 111, Folder 4)
  - Sprinkle, Annie. Post Porn Modernist, 1991 (Box 111, Folder 5)
  - Sprinkle, Annie. Spectacular Sex, 2005 (Box 111, Folder 6)
  - Theories and documents of contemporary art, 1996 (Box 111, Folder 7)
  - Theory and Flesh, Winter 1986 (Box 116, Folder 7)
  - Theory and Flesh, April 1986 (Box 116, Folder 8)
  - Theory and Flesh, 1985 (Box 116, Folder 6)
  - Theory and Flesh, 1986 (Box 116, Folder 9)
  - Theory and Flesh, 1986 (Box 116, Folder 10)
  - Unison, October 1989 (Box 111, Folder 9)
  - Unison, April-July 1988 (Box 111, Folder 8)
  - Vision, 1975 (Box 111, Folder 10)
  - Wack!, 2007 (Box 113, Folder 1)
  - Wasserman, Marion Claire. Prana, 2015 (Box 115, Folder 9)
  - Weirmeir, Jude. Issue 19, 2013 (Box 114, Folder 5)
  - Wine Wise, 2008 (Box 111, Folder 11)
- OVERSIZE Series I: Art Practice, 267723
  - OVERSIZE Subseries A: Art Administration, 268904
    - Oversize Handwritten Performance Ideas, undated; 271267 (Box 73, Folder 1)
  - OVERSIZE Subseries B: Writing, 267889
    - 7 Chakra Flower Prayers, undated; 271498 (Box 81)
    - "7 Chakras Prayers", undated; 271519 (Folder 16)
    - 7 Years of Living Art Performance Posters, undated; 271266 (Box 73, Folder 2)
    - Art In Everyday Life Annotated Galley Proof: Title Page, [1981]; 271586 (Box 85, Folder 3)
    - Art In Everyday Life Annotated Galley Proof: Pages 1-8, [1981]; 271587 (Box 85, Folder 4)
    - Art In Everyday Life Annotated Galley Proof: Pages 9- 15, [1981]; 271588 (Box 85, Folder 5)
    - Art In Everyday Life Annotated Galley Proof: Pages 16- 24, [1981]; 271589 (Box 85, Folder 6)
    - Art In Everyday Life Annotated Galley Proof: Pages 25- 32, [1981]; 271590 (Box 85, Folder 7)
    - Art In Everyday Life Annotated Galley Proof: Pages 33- 40, [1981]; 271591 (Box 85, Folder 8)
    - Art In Everyday Life Annotated Galley Proof: Pages 41- 48, [1981]; 271592 (Box 85, Folder 9)
    - Art In Everyday Life Annotated Galley Proof: Pages 49- 56, [1981]; 271593 (Box 85, Folder 10)
    - Art In Everyday Life Annotated Galley Proof: Pages 57- 64, [1981]; 271594 (Box 85, Folder 11)
    - Art In Everyday Life Annotated Galley Proof: Pages 65-72, [1981]; 271595 (Box 85, Folder 12)
    - Art In Everyday Life Annotated Galley Proof: Pages 73- 80, [1981]; 271596 (Box 85, Folder 13)
    - Art In Everyday Life Annotated Galley Proof: Pages 81- 88, [1981]; 271597 (Box 85, Folder 14)
    - Art In Everyday Life Annotated Galley Proof: Pages 89- 96, [1981]; 271598 (Box 85, Folder 15)
    - Art In Everyday Life Annotated Galley Proof: Pages 97- 104, 271599 (Box 85, Folder 16)
    - Art In Everyday Life Annotated Galley Proof: Pages 105- 112, [1981]; 271600 (Box 85, Folder 17)
    - Art In Everyday Life Annotated Galley Proof: Pages 113- 120, [1981]; 271601 (Box 85, Folder 18)
    - Art In Everyday Life Annotated Galley Proof: Pages 121- 128, [1981]; 271602 (Box 85, Folder 19)
    - Art In Everyday Life Annotated Galley Proof: Pages 129- 136, [1981]; 271603 (Box 85, Folder 20)
    - Art In Everyday Life Annotated Galley Proof: Pages 137- 144, [1981]; 271604 (Box 85, Folder 21)
    - Art In Everyday Life Annotated Galley Proof: Pages 145- 152, [1981]; 271605 (Box 85, Folder 22)
    - Photo for Galleys: You Too Are a Performance Artist, undated; 271268 (Box 73, Folder 3)
    - "System:matic Extracises", undated; 271499 (Box 81)
  - OVERSIZE Subseries D: Press, 267724
    - Promotional Posters, 1980-1989; 271325 (Box 76, Folder 1)
    - Promotional Posters, 1990-1999; 271326 (Box 76, Folder 2)
    - Promotional Posters, 2000-2013; 271327 (Box 76, Folder 3)
    - Promotional Posters, undated; 271328 (Box 76, Folder 4)
    - Promotional Posters, 1989-2002; 271517 (Folder 14)
      Snug Harbor Cultural Center "Outside the Frame: Performance and the Object," Exit Art "The End Is the Beginning," University Gallery Events and Exhibitions Poster, and Exit Art "Reactions."
    - Publicity: La Mamelle Performance Vol. 1, No. 4 and The Brooklyn Rail, Feb. 2012, 1976, 2012; 271329 (Box 76, Folder 5)
  - OVERSIZE Subseries F: Photos, 267725
    - 7 Years of Living Art Photograph, undated; 271272 (Box 73, Folder 4)
    - Annotated Photograph Album, [1942-1970]; 271511 (Box 84)